Craig Seymour Collection, 1968-2006 SC 144
Archives of African American Music and Culture
- 4. Interviews
  - 4.11. Interviews related to Lil' Mo
    - Lil' Mo, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with Lil' Mo (Cynthia Loving).
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/z01069fm6x
    - Unidentified Lil' Mo fans, circa 2000; 1 Audiocassette; Interview about Lil' Mo
      cass 2064 A
  - 4.12. Interviews related to Luther Vandross
    - Christine Wiltshire, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with singer Christine Wiltshire discusses how she began singing backup with Vandross, her own musical career, and Vandross generally. Very frank discussion of Vandross's personal life and career.
      cass 2162 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/712m219x9z
    - Cissy Houston, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Cissy Houston about Luther Vandross.
      cass 2157 A; cass 2166 A
      cass 2166: https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/d27881253r
      cass 2157: https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r66j03kd9t
      Content duplicated between cass 2157 and cass 2166.
    - Clive Davis, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Clive Davis about why he chose to work with Luther Vandross and Vandross's success.
      cass 2159 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p19326s761
    - David Nathan, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with David Nathan discussing how he met Luther Vandross, his interviews with Luther, Luther's music, Luther's dating life, etc.
      cass 2158 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/z70890z42k
    - David Nathan, 1 Audiocassette; 2nd interview with David Nathan about interviews he conducted with Luther Vandross, musicians Vandross produced, Vandross' personality, etc.
      cass 2161 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/039k12fj1x
    - David Sanborn, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with saxophonist David Sanborn discussing his work with David Bowie and Luther Vandross.
      cass 2165 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/z60c87w33r
    - Delores Hall, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with actress and singer Delores Hall, discussing having Luther sing back-up for her, his work, her own work with Harry Belafonte, etc.
      cass 2167 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/h93g94q63d
    - Jaheim, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about Jaheim's rise to fame singing Luther Vandross songs and Vandross' impact on Jaheim's career.
    - Luther Vandross, 2 Audiocassettes; In-person interview with Vandross discussing his international success, recording, R&B vs. disco vs. soul, working with Bette Middler and David Bowie, weight issues, live performance in Jamaica, his health, etc.
      cass 2156 A/B; cass 2157 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r66j03kd9t
    - Luther Vandross, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Vandross about his upcoming show in Buffalo, NY, Sept 11, touring/promotion, etc.
      cass 2157 A
    - Michael Brauer, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with mix engineer Michael Brauer discussing Media Sound, studio engineers, working with Luther Vandross.
      cass 2164 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p88c488n78
    - Mike Garson, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with pianist Mike Garson discussing his work with David Bowie and Luther Vandross.
      cass 2168 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/m21465br2k
    - Patrick Adams, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with producer Patrick Adams about Luther Vandross.
      cass 2148 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/w22v145920
    - Phoebe Snow, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Phoebe Snow discussing Vandross's health, his work, Snow's work in jingles and advertising, and Snow's recording of "Whether Or Not The World Gets Better".
      cass 2165 A
    - Stanley Bennet Clay, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Stanley Bennet Clay about Luther Vandross.
      cass 2161
    - Vince Aletti, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with record executive and journalist Vince Aletti, discussing the band Change, RFC, Ray Caviano, etc.
      cass 2163 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/z01069fm77
    - Wayne Garfield, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Wayne Garfield discussing the track "Glow of Love" that Vandross sang with Change and on which Garfield was lyricist. Garfield discusses Vandross's sexuality off the record.
  - 4.13. Interviews related to Mariah Carey
    - David Morales, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Morales, who did Mariah's remixes
      cass 2141 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/n49t058p56
    - Don Lenne, 1 Audiocassette; Interview about Maria Carey's tenure at Sony.
    - Jimmy Jam, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview, discusses his work with Mariah Carey
      cass 2141 B
    - Kandi Burruss, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview discussing her collaboration with Mariah.
    - Mariah Carey, circa 1999; 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with Mariah Carey about her then-recent album Rainbow (1999), including remixes and videos.
      cass 2093 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r96712sf0p
    - Unidentified interviewee, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about Mariah Carey with editor, Global Dance and staff writer, DMA
  - 4.14. Interviews related to Mary J. Blige
    - Carl E. "Chucky" Thompson, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with Carl E. "Chucky" Thompson (producer) discussing working with Mary J. Blige, TLC, etc.
      cass 2120 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/494v53n549
    - Etta James, 1 Audiocassette; Interview via telephone about Mary J. Blige and other hip-hop artists.
      cass 2068 B; cass 2120 B
      cass 2068: https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/n59q08cg8g
      cass 2120: https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/494v53n549
      Content duplicated across cass 2068 and cass 2120.
    - LaTonya Blige, approximately 1999-2000; 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Mary J. Blige's sister, LaTonya, about Blige's album My Life.
      cass 2088 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/989r07739k
    - Mary J. Blige, approximately 1999-2000; 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Seymour for Spin magazine article; discussion about her album My Life and Missy Elliot.
    - Mary J. Blige, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about lessons she's learned about the music industry.
    - Mary J. Blige, 1 Audiocassette; Short conversation about an earlier interview.
      cass 2139 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/772039n82q
    - Tony Maserati, Phone interview with record producer Maserati, discusses his work with Mary J. Blige on her album My Life.
      cass 2101 A; cass 2139 A
      cass 2101: https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/900n79pd9x
      cass 2139: https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/772039n82q
      Content duplicated across cass 2101 and cass 2139.
    - Unidentified woman, 1 Audiocassette; Discussing the inclusion of Blige's cover of "You Make Me Feel Like a Natural Woman" on the New York Undercover soundtrack.
  - 4.15. Interviews related to Monica
    - Clive Davis, 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview about Monica.
      cass 2074 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/316p98fn2r
    - Jermaine "JD" Dupri, 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview about Jimmy Jam and Terry Lewis's influence on his work and the industry. Interview ends with JD discussing Monica.
    - Monica, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview about being a child star, her work, etc.
      cass 2085 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/q77f75xm50
    - Monica, circa 1999; 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about Monica's upcoming performance at a World AIDS Day benefit, probably in 1999 when she performed at "Music With A Message" with Wyclef Jean and Destiny's Child.
      cass 2097 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/c08h44679z
    - Monica, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview about her album All Eyez On Me (2002).
      cass 2130 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/861267d22m
    - Monica's [mother?], 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with Monica's [mother?].
      cass 2154 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/514n59wb8h
  - 4.16. Interviews related to Nelly Furtado
    - Amy Gasparelli, 1 Audiocassette; Fan interview about Nelly Furtado.
      cass 2136 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/663405v976
    - David Browne, 1 Audiocassette; Interview with David Browne (music critic) about Nelly Furtado's work.
      cass 2136 B
    - Geoff Mayfield, 1 Audiocassette; Interview with Geoff Mayfield from Billboard about Cher's and Nelly Furtado's work.
    - Nelly Furtado, 1 Audiocassette; Interview about her work and Mary J Blige.
    - Unidentified editor, 1 Audiocassette; Discussion between Seymour and [his editor?] about his upcoming article [on Nelly Furtado?]
    - Unidentified woman, 1 Audiocassette; Discussion with unidentified videographer or photographer about Nelly Furtado and her critical reception.
  - 4.17. Interviews related to Notorious B.I.G.
    - Frank [?], 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Frank [?] (host of a call-in show, possibly on MTV) on the events surrounding the death of Notorious B.I.G.
    - Voletta Wallace, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with Voletta Wallace (Notorious B.I.G.'s mother) about his posthumous album Born Again.
      cass 2094 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/781w42td57
    - Unidentified woman, 1 Audiocassette; Interview discussing the events surrounding the death of Notorious B.I.G.
    - Unidentified morning show host, 1 Audiocassette; Interview discussing the events surrounding the death of Notorious B.I.G.
    - Unidentified author, 1 Audiocassette; Interview discussing the events surrounding the death of Notorious B.I.G.
    - Unidentified representative of [The Firm?], 1 Audiocassette; Interview discussing the events surrounding the death of Notorious B.I.G.
  - 4.18. Interviews related to Outkast
    - Andre 3000 (Andre Benjamin, formerly Dre of Outkast), 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with Dre about Outkast's work, particularly Aquemini and Stankonia.
      cass 2077 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/217q67qz6w
    - Antonio "L.A." Reid, 1 Audiocassette; Interview about his relationship with Outkast.
      cass 2155 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/v73b98sn5k
    - Big Boi of Outkast, 1 Audiocassette; Interview about Speakerboxx/The Love Below and winning Album of the Year.
      cass 2133 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r46q97f549
    - Michael "Blue" Williams, 1 Audiocassette; Interview discussing trajectory of Outkast's singles and albums and Williams' work as a manager.
      cass 2083 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/q77f75xm4p
    - Shanti Das, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about coming to Motown/Universal, her work with Outkast and other artists in the music industry.
      cass 2138 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/s55m31735x
    - Unnamed MTV employee, 1 Audiocassette; Phone conversation discussing a future interview about Outkast.
      cass 2107 A
  - 4.19. Interviews related to Pet Shop Boys
    - Neil Tennant, 1 Audiocassette; Interview about new Pet Shop Boys album.
      cass 2080 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/r36t94c66f
    - Robin Wilson, 1 Audiocassette; Interview with record store manager about Pet Shop Boys
  - 4.20. Interviews related to the Rolling Stones
    - Jon Goff, 2002; 1 Audiocassette; Interview about attending Rolling Stones concerts.
      cass 2062 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/643999tb19
    - Keith Cummings, 2002; 1 Audiocassette; Seymour leaves message for Cummings requesting a call back.
      cass 2062 B
    - Lowell Brown, 2002; 1 Audiocassette; Interview about attending Rolling Stones concerts.
      cass 2062 A/B
    - Mick Jagger, 2002; 1 Audiocassette; Interview via telephone, largely about the Rolling Stones. Interview likely during their Forty Licks tour.
  - 4.21. Interviews related to Spelman production of Flying Over Purgatory
    - Casandra Echols, 2002; 1 Audiocassette; Interview with Spelman student actress Casandra Echols about Ruby Dee and Flying Over Purgatory.
      cass 2169 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/x816639j4w
    - Ruby Dee and Ayoka Chenzira, 2002; 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with actress Ruby Dee and filmmaker Ayoka Chenzira, discussing the production of Flying Over Purgatory at Spelman, black cinema and theatre.
      cass 2169 A/B
    - Sharon Warren, 2002; 1 Audiocassette; Interview with actress Sharon Warren about her entry into the acting profession, Flying Over Purgatory, and Ruby Dee.
    - Unidentified South African actress, 2002; 1 Audiocassette; Interview with unidentified South African actress about her experiences in South Africa and coming to Atlanta for the production of Flying Over Purgatory.
  - 4.22. Interviews related to Sum 41
    - Edgefest representative, 1 Audiocassette; Discussion of Sum 41 playing Edgefest, their singles, and their impact.
      cass 2103 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k22534nd8b
    - MTV representative, 1 Audiocassette; Discussion of Sum 41 on MTV, being picked to play Edgefest, their singles, and their impact.
    - Unidentified Sum 41 band member, 1 Audiocassette; Discussion of Sum 41s tour with other punk bands, their albums.
  - 4.23. Interviews related to The Supremes
    - Harry [Weinger?], 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Harry [Weinger?] about Supremes box set [interviewee probably producer]
      cass 2125 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/q77f75xm3c
    - Lynda Laurence, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with singer Lynda Laurence from the Supremes on the Supremes box set and the recent reunion tour.
      cass 2125 B
    - Mary Wilson, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about the importance of the Supremes.
      cass 2111 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/x21t44w23r
    - Scherrie Payne, circa 2000; 1 Audiocassette; Interview via telephone, discusses The Supremes, Diana Ross, Supremes box set release.
      cass 2063 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/742930j81v
    - Susaye Green, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about the Supremes, their box set, and her post-Supremes work.
      cass 2111 B
    - Unidentified man (producer? Manager?), circa 2000; 1 Audiocassette; Discusses the Supremes tour in 2000 without Cindy Birdsong and Mary Wilson.
      cass 2102 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/t84871540m
    - Unidentified man (affiliated with Motown Alumni Association), circa 2000; 1 Audiocassette; Discusses the Supremes 2000 tour.
    - Unidentified man, circa 2000; 1 Audiocassette; Discusses the Supremes 2000 tour.
      cass 2102 A/B
  - 4.24. Interviews related to TLC
    - Bill Diggins, 2000-04; 1 Audiocassette; Bill Diggins was TLC's manager. Telephone interview, discusses a conference call with the surviving members of TLC, arrangements for Lopes's body.
      cass 2080 A
    - Chilli [Rozanda Thomas], 2000-04; 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview about the death of Lisa Lopes.
    - Dallas Austin, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Dallas Austin (record producer) about TLC and their album Crazysexycool.
      cass 2082 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k41z40s66k
    - Dallas Austin, 1 Audiocassette; Dallas Austin discussing TLC's 2002 album 3D.
    - Family members of Lisa Lopez, 2000-04; 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview about the death of Lisa Lopes.
    - [Jimmy Douglas? (producer with TLC?)], 2000-04; 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview, discusses Lisa Lopes's death, their last album.
    - L.A. Reid, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with L.A. Reid (co-founder LaFace Records) about TLC and their album Crazysexycool.
    - Lisa "Left Eye" Lopes, 2000-2001?; 2 Audiocassettes; [In-person?] interview, discusses leaving TLC, her solo albums.
      cass 2067, cass 2147
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/z80594136h
    - Lisa "Left Eye" Lopes, circa 2000; 1 Audiocassette; Interview with Lisa "Left Eye" Lopes of TLC discussing the album CrazySexyCool (1994).
    - Natina Reed, 2000-04; 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview about the death of Lisa Lopes.
    - Tionne "T-Boz" Watkins, circa 2000; 1 Audiocassette; Interview with Tionne "T-Boz" Watkins of TLC discussing the album CrazySexyCool (1994).
    - Unidentified publicist, 2000-04; 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview with a publicist about the funeral for Lisa Lopes
  - 4.25. Miscellaneous interviews for articles
    - Admin Asst for Chris Chambers, 1 Audiocassette; Phone call with admin asst for Chris Chambers (then SVP of Publicity and Artist Development at Sony) discussing of songwriting/production credits for Usher song.
    - Allison Moorer, 1 Audiocassette; Discussion of her 2002 album Miss Fortune.
      cass 2124 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/890r76mj60
    - Amerie, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with Amerie Mi Marie Rogers discusses living in D.C., her music, performing, etc.
      cass 2143 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/217q67qz5k
    - Amil, 2000?; 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Amil Whitehead (rapper) about her debut album, her work with Jay-Z, etc.
      cass 2108 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/z40k81qt6q
    - Ann Nesby, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with Ann Nesby about her gospel, R&B, and acting work.
      cass 2144 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p68k424v2v
    - Athena Lipari, 1 Audiocassette; In-person fan interview about Lee Ann Womack.
      cass 2126 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/821g553p4t
    - Billie Woodruff, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Woodruff (music video director) about imaging and video in R&B and hip hop, Kelly Price, BET and MTV. Part of Seymour's research for article about Kelly Price.
      cass 2114 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/j62s166f13
    - Blu Cantrell, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview, discusses the state of R&B, her own work, etc.
      cass 2104 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/s16118xs09
    - Brad Martin, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview at a week-long country music festival, his album Wings of a Honky-Tonk Angel.
      cass 2126 B
    - Celeda (Victoria Sharpe), 1 Audiocassette; Interview with the drag performer about her album and singles.
      cass 2134 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/920f85tf5k
    - Chaka Khan, 2004?; 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Chaka Khan (Duplicate of content on 2088 B)
      cass 2088 B; cass 2112 A
      cass 2112: https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/c67w62mj37
      cass 2088: https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/989r07739k
      Content is duplicated across cass 2088 and cass 2112.
    - Chuck [?], 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview discussing boy bands.
      cass 2102 B
    - Chuck D, 1 Audiocassette; Interview with Chuck D about Elvis.
    - CL Smooth, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with CL Smooth (of Pete Rock & CL Smooth) about the album Mecca and the Soul Brother.
      cass 2086 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/g94h640973
    - Craig Seymour, 1999?; Seymour being interviewed about his job at the National Lesbian and Gay Journalists Association.
      Content is duplicated across cass 2068 and cass 2120.
    - Dallas Austin, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about the ousting of Clive Davis the head of Arista Records and the installation of L.A. Reid as President and CEO.
      cass 2094 B
    - Dan Tyminski, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Dan Tyminski (Alison Krause band) on the O Brother Where Art Thou? Soundtrack.
      cass 2132
    - Danny Grady, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview with Danny Grady (of Atlanta-based rock band Injected) about their album Burn it Black.
    - David Ritz, 2001; 1 Audiocassette; Ritz is a Marvin Gaye biographer. Interview via telphone, discusses the continued success of Gaye's music, including the 2001 Motown deluxe edition re-issue. Continues on side B. Ritz gives his email, phone, and address at the end of the interview.
      cass 2069 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/m70m80q568
    - Deana Carter, 1 Audiocassette; Deana Carter discussing her then-recent projects, including recording and acting projects like The Badge (2002).
    - Delroy Lindo, 1 Audiocassette; Interview about the then-recent movie "Romeo Must Die." Interviewer not Craig Seymour, or possibly group interview with Seymour and other journalists.
      cass 2089 A
    - Destiny's Child, 1 Audiocassette; phone interview with members of Destiny's Child about their album 8 Days of Christmas (2001) and Survivor (2001), their solo projects.
      cass 2112 B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/c67w62mj37
    - Donnie, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with musician Donnie ("The Colored Section") about his recent work, being gay and black.
      cass 2096 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/5644757t5n
    - E. Lynn Harris, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with the author on his life, his work, his memoir, etc. Some discussion of Luther Vandross.
      cass 2142 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/j13900v81q
    - Eve, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with Eve (Eve Jeffers), discussing her music and acting work.
      cass 2087 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k22534nd71
    - Faith [Evans?], 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about her work and recent album (Faithfully, 2001?).
      cass 2129 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/b78t34zt4x
    - Gary Bongiovanni, 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview with Editor-in-Chief of Pollstar about bands from the 80s touring successfully recently.
    - Gerald Albright, 1 Audiocassette; Telephone interview about jazz.
    - Greg Green, 1 Audiocassette; Interview with Greg Green (director of booking Masquerade in Atlanta) phone interview about their 80s new wave night.
    - Hoobastank, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with Markku Lappalainen and Chris Hesse about recent shows, recording, etc.
      cass 2151 A
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/k32237q04j
    - Jagged Edge, 1 Audiocassette; In-person interview with members of Jagged Edge (Brian and Brandon Casey?) about R&B and neo-soul music, their own work, etc.
      cass 2106 A/B
      https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/p09623qg0b
    - Jimmy Jam, 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview about his Essence Award, Janet Jackson, etc.
      cass 2152 B
    - Jody Watley, 1999-05-12; 1 Audiocassette; Phone interview prior to her performance at [DC?] Gay Pride, discusses her music, her gay following.
      cass 2084 A/B; cass 2140 A/B; cass 2109 A/B
      cass 2084: https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/x02138r25v
      cass 2140: https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/v43n89kn0n
      cass 2109: https://purl.dlib.indiana.edu/iudl/media/t54k61z251
      cass 2084 and cass 2140 duplicates of each other. cass 2109 dubbed from either cass 2084 or cass 2140 and some interview content was cut off at the end.
    - Joel Silver and Jet Li, 1 Audiocassette; Interview about the then-recent movie "Romeo Must Die." Interviewer not Craig Seymour, or possibly group interview with Seymour and other journalists.
    - John Mellencamp, 1 Audiocassette; Interview via telephone, discusses his collaborations (Chuck D, India Arie, etc.), songs about race. Interview just prior to the release of Cuttin' Heads (2001).
      cass 2069 B
    - Johnny Gray, 1 Audiocassette; Johnny Gray (music director WKHX-FM, Atlanta) discussing country music's themes and popularity post-9/11, popular country arists, etc.
      cass 2117 A